There you are.
P.E.'s already started.
They threw my gym clothes in the garbage.
Did they?
You're right, I remember that now.
Everyone's having so much fun. I hate them.
I did, didn't I?
I hate people in cliques, too.
Because it made me feel like I was
getting excluded for no good reason.
I hate breaks, too.
Because it felt like everyone was
pointing out how isolated I was.
I hated teachers, too, because
they made us work in groups,
and I'd get excluded.
I especially hated special events at school.
Thinking back on those days, I can't
remember a single thing I didn't hate.
Nobody needs me around, anyway.
Can I just die?
You should probably hold off on dying.
Wait a little longer and you'll make
a friend. An annoying one, but still.
You'll also meet a tall guy who's
kind and a girl who's friendly,
and a kinda-cowardly student council
president and his little posse.
Lots of people will want to be friends with you.
Not only that,
but you'll meet someone
who cries for you, laughs for you,
gets sad for you, gets mad for you,
and scolds you when you need scolding.
She's waiting for you, I promise.
If that's true, then...
Then...
Huh? What was I just dreaming about?
I wanna see Hori-san.
"Horimiya"
The boy I love is really weak.
Really, really weak.
He doesn't actually like yelling at people.
He'll laugh about being unathletic,
when really, he wishes he wasn't.
Boys and girls alike all fawn over him,
which makes him happy,
but every now and then,
it makes him feel anxious.
"The Truth Deception Reveals"
There's so much he struggles with,
and I love him so much.
O-Oh, no! Sengoku-kun, get it, I'm scared!
His expression screams "I'm scared, too!"
But...
That really freaked him out. Good job.
The boy I love is weak,
but he tries really hard.
But you know,
back when we met,
he was a totally different person.
Man, I have such a crush on Ayasaki.
Her face is so tiny and cute, you know?
Yeah, totally!
She's so hard to approach, though.
Like, she thinks she's too good for us.
Probably 'cause she knows all
the guys have the hots for her.
Out of all the girls,
Ayasaki and Kono really stick out.
They're like Beauty and the Beast.
You think so? They're both pretty normal.
C'mon, dude, Ayasaki's super hot.
Not really. They both look normal.
What were you reading in class just now?
Some manga?
Goethe.
Gerta? What's that?
Goethe. He's an author.
Oh, that's not the name of the book. Is it good?
Do you like to read, too, Ayasaki-san?
Not during class, but yeah, I like reading.
Like Grimm's Fairy Tales.
You mean like, Snow White?
Yeah, like Snow White.
"Snow White"
I brought these for you to borrow.
Really?
There are a bunch of stories in there,
so hopefully you'll find one you like.
Wow, thanks!
That'll be a fun read, Remi.
Yeah!
Oh, do you like books like these, too, Kono-san?
Wait, me? Yeah.
Then you can borrow them after Ayasaki-san.
I really like the third story in
the collection. It's really captivating.
Wait, are you sure?
Yeah.
Th-Thanks.
You're welcome.
I really liked these. Thanks!
Then here, read these next.
Whoa, more books?! Sweet!
How many books do you own?
They're mostly my parents'. We have
a whole room full of them at my house.
Really? I wish I could see.
You want to? You can.
Oh, don't worry; I won't be
weird about it or anything!
Oh, uh, sure, got it.
"Sengoku"
Wow, you really do have a whole roomful!
We haven't cleaned in here much,
so watch out for the dust.
Are you okay?!
I'm fine! I shouldn't have
touched without asking.
I just wanted to see this one book.
Oh, that one's really old.
What's it about?
The day before the world ends, I think?
Is it the whole world,
or just Japan that gets destroyed?
Think it's the whole world.
Everyone goes into a panic.
If you knew the world was going to end tomorrow,
you probably wouldn't feel like
doing much of anything, huh?
You think so? I'd wanna
blow through all my money.
And I'd load up on desserts, too.
Huh? You're spending your
last day on Earth eating dessert?!
There are tons I've never tried! Might as well!
I see.
Are your pigtails up higher today?
Y-Yeah, I just felt like it.
I like it. It looks nice!
Really?!
If you're cute, you can do
whatever, you'll still be cute!
Guess you don't understand where
I'm coming from, though, Sengoku-kun.
Sorry to interrupt! Can I borrow you?
Thanks for lending these to me! I read 'em all.
You didn't have to rush through them.
I didn't! They were so good,
I ended up on a reading binge.
Man, though, I really wouldn't
want the world to end tomorrow!
What about all those desserts, though?
The end of the world is no time for desserts!
Kamioka has a crush on you, Ayasaki-san.
Mmkay.
Hey, can I go over to your
place again today, Sengoku-kun?
Sure.
Just, I know you're used
to talking to guys, Ayasaki-san,
but I might get the wrong
idea about your intentions.
You'll like this series, Ayasaki-san.
It's long, but totally worth the read.
Can't wait to read it, then.
Hey, Sengoku-kun?
So, Sengoku-kun, I, uh...
What is it?
Nothing, just, uh, what if--
What if the world was gonna end
tomorrow? What would you do?
Huh? Oh, you mean like that book?
I mean, kind of, but... sure.
I'd tell you I liked you.
Then I'd turn to space dust.
The end.
Was that a joke?
No.
It wasn't.
Never mind, just forget it!
Why're you so embarrassed?
I-I am not embarrassed!
C'mon, don't lie.
I'm not lying! I'm not embarrassed at all!
I know you are. Your face is all red!
I'm glad.
Yeah, sure.
You know,
I like you, too, Sengoku-kun!
I like you, too, Remi.
"Through the Seasons With You"
Here. Thanks for letting me borrow it.
Huh? You finished it in just one day?!
I finished studying early,
so I had some extra time.
Oh, cool. What'd you think
of this bestselling tearjerker?
It was okay.
He's lying.
He cried while reading it last night.
When we met, he didn't get swept away
by those around him. I loved him then.
And I love who he is now, too.
His weak points, the fact that
he can't lie, how hard he tries--
I love all of him.
So... why the sudden urge to give me a manicure?
Well, I was cleaning my room
and found some unopened bottles.
I thought this color'd look good on you.
Okay.
O-Oh, no.
I shouldn't, but I want to.
She'd be so mad.
Miyamura, other foot!
But...
Miyamura?
Gimme your other foot, c'mon--
"PLOP"
I thought if I stepped on you...
I'd get enough EXP to level up.
What?
I'm kidding! I'm so sorry!
You're always messing with me,
so I figured I'd try messing with you today!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
It's okay, I'm not, like, mad.
I'm just kind of surprised.
Plus, like, you're always going off
on Shindo-kun and Sawada-san,
but when you're with me,
you're so calm and well-mannered,
so are you, like, faking it for me?
Is this not you?
No, this is the real me, I promise.
Oh.
I mean, would you rather
I yelled at you and hit you instead?
No, definitely--
Goddamn. C'mon, Kyoko!
Who the hell d'ya think
you're talking to, bitch?!
Actually, that's kind of hot.
What?!
Mornin', Miyamura.
Hey. How's it hangin', Ishikawa?
Fine.
Damn, dude,
you still listening to this, Iura?
I mean, it's all bangers, but damn.
--Dude.
--I have no idea, man!
Oh, Miyamura-kun. Could I please
borrow your Math B textbook?
Man, seriously, Prez? You forgot yours?
Get your shit together, man!
Ishikawa-kun!
Don't look at me! I got no clue what's going on!
What's up with you today, Miyamura?
"Gloom"
Kill me.
Huh?
I'm guessing this is something Her Highness
the Ice Queen wanted you to do.
Yep.
If you don't want to do this,
then you should tell her.
Morning!
I'm begging you, Ishikawa-kun, get it together!
Stop making this my problem!
Wow, it was that tough?
Guess I'll never get to see you
get all violent with me, then.
Well, I'll just wait for you
to forget, then give it a try.
Really?! Oh, man, I can't wait!
Later.
See ya!
Yup!
Wait, I don't think the physics
room is open during lunch.
What? Oh, I think you're right!
Ugh, I'll drop these off after lunch.
Just tell our teacher I'll be late.
Want me to go instead?
Nah, I got it.
"Sigh"
Excuse me. Do you have a moment?
Huh?
Wait, hold on. Is this it?
Is now the time to try that?
But how should I act? What would make her happy?
Oh, hey, remember that--
Who the hell do you think you're
talking to, you frickin' airhead?!
Stop actin' like we're all buddy-buddy,
'cause we're not! Now shut the hell up!
Hori-san, I really can't do this!
That's the last time I'm gonna yell at you.
Hori-san... I'm so lost.
And now they're all talking about
how we were fighting in the AV room.
I feel bad for freaking out the underclassmen.
What's up, Yuki?
Huh?
Oh, just...
Just what?
You got asked out?
Yeah, four days ago.
That long ago?
Don't leave him hanging.
W-Well, I have to go turn him down!
Huh? You're turning him down?
Of course I am! I don't even know him.
He looked, like, really serious, too.
I just feel bad going up to him
with only a "Sorry, no dice!"
Why don't you have someone
pretend to be your boyfriend?
Like Toru!
Oh, he'd hate that.
I don't think he would, as long
as you explained what's going on.
I dunno...
Yeah, it's happening after school.
Yup. See ya then.
Ishikawa-kun's in.
That was fast!
So, what do you want me to do?
Just kind of feel her up
while she turns him down.
Calm down, Satan!
I can't do him dirty like that!
C'mon, Hori!
So what class is he in?
Class 6, I think?
Yeah, Class 6. His name's Yanagi-kun.
Hold on, Yoshikawa. You sure
you wanna use me for this?
Wouldn't you want, like, a way
hotter guy to pull this off?
W-Well, you're definitely a little
hotter than him, so it's fine!
Oh. 'Kay.
Just a little! Just a little, okay?!
Heard you loud and clear.
Shouldn't we head out already?
Yeah.
Wait, you're coming, too?!
"I wanna see who it is!"
Heck yeah! I'm worried about you!
Oh. Thanks, Hori.
Okay, let's go.
Huh?
We're dating, right? Just for today.
I forget who's even in Class 6.
Yeah, hard to remember
when they're not in your class.
Maybe Ayasaki-san knows?
Just for today.
You don't have to say anything, Toru.
You sure?
Yeah. Sorry for making
you go along with all this.
You better be sorry.
Let me say just one thing to him, then.
Like, "She's my girlfriend." That okay?
What?!
Y-You just have to pretend
to be my boyfriend, you know!
Yeah. That's pretending.
Sure, whatever, say it!
I can't hear what they're saying.
Oh, there he is!
I'm so sorry I'm late, Yoshikawa-san!
Our teacher needed me for something.
"S H O C K"
Holy crap, he's gorgeous!
He's a zillion times hotter than Toru!
C'mon.
Um, uh, I'm...
Oh, hello. I'm Akane Yanagi from Class 6.
God, even his name is cool!
I'm Ishikawa.
Miyamura's the pretty guy in our group,
and even he pales in comparison!
Hang in there, Ishikawa-kun!
So you have a boyfriend.
Yeah. Sorry.
I'm genetically inferior on every level!
Why should I bother existing?!
Hell, if he asked me out, I'd say yes!
What are you, blind, Yoshikawa?!
I guess that's that, then.
I mean, Ishikawa-kun is
a lot more attractive than me.
Stop, I'm already dead!
I'd better get going.
Oh, okay.
Yuki!
Why'd you turn him down?! He's a total hottie!
Huh?! Oh... he's kind of too hot, you know?
And I'm not into like, fancy,
expensive food and stuff.
She's a total pleb.
God, for a second there,
I thought I'd just died on the spot.
That really scared me. He was way too hot.
I had no idea we had
someone like that in our grade.
Yanagi-kun?
Yeah, I know him.
He's super hot and totally hilarious.
Hilarious?
"WHACK"
Ouch!
Yanagi, where're your glasses?
Oh, I haven't bought a new pair yet...
But I'm okay, I don't need them that--
Yanagi!
That happens all the time.
All the time?
His eyesight's really bad.
He's practically blind.
He is, huh?
H-Hey!
Yes?
I think you might've had the wrong girl.
S-So there's this friend of mine, Kyoko Hori.
She's way taller than me,
and way prettier than me, too.
A-Are you sure you didn't mean to ask her out?
Huh? Wait, why are you asking?
Oh, I'm guessing you heard
how bad my eyes are, huh...
I didn't have the wrong person.
Huh?
I've liked you for quite a while.
So I know what you look like,
but I don't know who this
Hori-san girl is you're talking about.
O-Oh. Okay.
Yuki!
Hori!
Oh, sorry! Didn't mean to interrupt.
Hey, it's Yanagi-kun.
Hori-san? We were just talking about you.
Yoshikawa-san said she had
an attractive female friend...
Hello. I'm Miyamura.
Oh, I'm sorry!
Ishikawa-kun, you're here, too!
Nope, I'm Hori.
Sorry! Then who might you be?
Ishikawa. We literally met yesterday.
I'm so sorry, uh... Miyamura-kun!
He kinda needs glasses.
Only kinda?
Oh, right! I just happened to
run into Yoshikawa-san here!
I wasn't trying anything funny, I... huh?
Hori-san, where's Ishikawa-kun?
Over here.
This is hilarious.
--Oh, there you are! I'm so sorry!
--Look, it's fine, Yanagi-kun.
--I swear, nothing funny
was happening here, really!
--Calm down, man!
--I swear, nothing funny
was happening here, really!
--Calm down, man!
"Next Time: It's Hard, but Not Impossible"